Aastha Goyal (Aashi)

Ph. 021 08623321

Email Id. aastha2150@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://nz.linkedin.com/in/aastha-goyal-00398912a

GitHub: https://github.com/AasthaGoyal
Website: www.wanderer.netlify.com/
https://swaachcleaning.azurewebsites.net/

I want to be a Developer. I have worked with Desktop, Android and Web applications, strongest language being C#. I am currently in my third year doing bachelor's degree-specializing in Software development. My personal goal is to improve my programming skills on a professional level and create solutions that would improve the lifestyle of people along with improving the environment.

Technical Skills:

C# C++ CSS Java JSON PHP MySQL Git Bootstrap ASP.NET

JavaScript Python Tableau HTML Weka SQLite XAMPP Postman

Projects:

- 1. <u>Swaach cleaning website:</u> Website for a startup cleaning company situated in Auckland. Created using ASP.NET, C# and MySQL.
- 2. <u>Global Ocean Mobile App</u>: Android mobile application for an immigration company called Global Ocean which helps international students to apply for student visas, travel insurance and supports for investment and trading in New Zealand.
- 3. <u>Paradise restaurant mobile application:</u> This is an android mobile application created using Android Studio. I have used Java and XML to do the coding. Also, the data shown in the app is being fetched from web service online which has been created using XAMPP and MySQL. The data is being fetched using PHP files and Json.
- 4. <u>Kids Hangman application:</u> This is a desktop application made using C#. It consists of two parts Learn Math and Learn English made for kids to get a hand on for learning English and Math in a fun and interactive way.
- 5. <u>Countdown product management project:</u> This is a desktop application that can be used by any retailer store like Countdown and Pak N Save made using C# and SQLite. It can be used to manage and store all the information about the input and output of stocks including the data of staff and customers.
- 6. <u>Wanderer Web Application (SOT Create Camp)</u> An app to find safe places to go for swim nearby, or places to go for hike and cycling. Made using Json, HTML and React.js.
- 7. Quiz Application, hashing algorithm, Save the humans, Tic-Tac-Toe C#, C++ and SQLite

Education and Qualifications:

<u>Auckland Institute of Studies, Auckland NZ</u>
(<u>September 2016 – September 2019</u>)

Bachelor's in information technology Software Development

Ryan International School (2014 – 2016) High School Languages Known: Hindi and English

Achievements and Certificates:

- 1. Student Council member
- 2. Nationals certificate in Taekwondo (Martial art)
- 3. State certificate in Football
- 4. Salesperson to complete first 15 and 25 sales
- 5. Class Representative 3 times
- 6. Excellence scholarship certificate 2 times
- 7. Part of Summer of Tech Create Camp 2018

Previous Experience

Global Ocean Group Ltd

May 2019 - August 2019

Developer

I was developer in a team of three people which comprise of a designer, developer and a system tester for the project to create a android mobile app for the company.

NZ Transport Agency - Mode + Alt + Shift Hackathon

March 2019

Developer

We as a team of 6 people worked on creating a solution that would encourage people to take public transport over private vehicle and reduce traffic congestion problems on New Zealand roads.

Summer of Tech – Create Camp

August 2018

Developer

We created a web application called Wanderer for tourists and enthusiasts to find good places to swim and visit, which can be accessed by the link above.

Student Council – Auckland Institutes of Studies

August 2017 – May 2018

Organizing events and orientations. Managing student management portal and resolving issues by organizing meeting with the executive team.

Goodview Trading NZ Ltd

June 2017 - December 2017

Website Supporter & Checkout Operator

Responsibilities:

- Handling Trade Me account for Goodview
- Making tax invoices, bill payments and purchase orders
- Customer service, Handling customer complaints and doubts

Achievements:

Confidence to communicate with people and resolve unexpected problems

Personal Interests: Sketching/Painting, reading novels, Football, Taekwondo, 3D designing

References

Kimberly Chang Adi Grover

Marketing officer-Indian Subcontinent Goodview Trading NZ Ltd.

Ph: (649) 815 1717 <u>kimberlyc@ais.ac.nz</u> Ph: (021) 2234892 <u>adi@goodview.co.nz</u>